chatliv.com 2018-08-24

# Theme

We are committed to protect your privacy when you visit our website and use available services.

We can add or remove services available on our website from time to time which may also lead to change in this privacy policy. We will still ensure to protect your privacy but we advise you to visit this privacy policy whenever you visit our website.

However, this Policy does not apply to the websites operated by third parties and their services which we are using. 

**Your agreement to this policy**

By using our services you unconditionally agree to this privacy policy. If not, then kindly don’t use our services.

**Collection of your information and its use:  **

We do not collect any information of our users when they visit our website. There is no registration required before using free services.

The chat application we are providing here is not hosted on our servers. This application is hosted on servers of coomeet.com. For detailed information on privacy policy and user agreement kindly visit following pages of www.coomeet.com

#### \- CooMeet Premium 

All **Premium Account and Subscription**  purchased on Chatliv through Coomeet video Dating App comes under [**Coomeet User Agreement**](https://coomeet.com/en/agreement) and Privacy Policy. Before Purchasing Their premium dating Service we request you read there **[Terms](https://coomeet.com/en/agreement)** and **[Policy](https://coomeet.com/en/privacypolicy)** first. 

Still we request you to kindly go through the following points also:

## Embedded content from other websites

This site may include embedded content (e.g. chat Applications, videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

## Cookie Policy -  Read more

  * Cookies : chatliv.com does not use cookies.

  * Third Party services/companies and websites : we may provide some services through third party companies or websites, the information collected by these third party websites, company or services provider is governed by their privacy policies, some of our third party services providers are (not limited to):

  1. \- Google Analytics | Google Adsense | Google Adwords : [Google Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en).
  2. \- Facebook.com: [facebook privacy policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/)
  3. \- lifestreetmedia.com | [lifestreetmedia privacy Policy](https://lifestreetmedia.com/privacy/)
  4. \- Mellowads.com | [Mellowads Terms](https://mellowads.com/terms) 

  *  Other Sites: This Privacy Policy applies to chatliv.com services only. We do not exercise control over the sites displayed on our web pages, sites that include applications, products or services, or links from within our various services. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you.
  * DoubleClick DART Cookie :Google, and other ads serving companies as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on chatliv.com ,Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to chatliv.com and other sites on the Internet, users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacy/ads/ ,other information on how to opt out available here: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp , Some of our advertising partners, third party services providers may use cookies and web beacons to collect data.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on chatliv.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

chatliv.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. chatliv.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. chatliv.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

As mentioned before, this privacy policy may change from time to time. 

If you have any questions, please feel free to contact us .

Last Updated: May-25-2018
